<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Halisi Wellness</string>


    <string-array name="title_articles">

        <item>Ficus pumila L. improves the prognosis of patients infected with HTLV-1, an RNA virus</item>
        <item>article2</item>
        <item>article3</item>
        <item>article4</item>
        <item>article5</item>
        <item>article6</item>
        <item>article7</item>
        <item>article8</item>
        <item>article9</item>
        <item>article10</item>
        <item>article11</item>
        <item>article12</item>
        <item>article13</item>
        <item>article14</item>
        <item>article15</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="details_articles">

        <item>Human T-cell leukemia virus type 1 was isolated as the retrovirus to be identified in humans. Here, we focused on Ficus pumila L. as a factor that be effective against human T-cell leukemia virus type 1. The significant and novel findings is that symptoms of patients with drinking Ficus pumila L. extracts did not worsen despite a lack of aggressive pharmacotherapy against adult T-cell leukemia, a human T-cell leukemia virus type 1-associated myelopathy, or T-cell leukemia virus type 1 uveitis. Twenty-eight of the 194 inpatients who underwent showed high levels of human T-cell leukemia virus type 1.

Among human T-cell leukemia virus type 1-infected patients, those who were administered Ficus pumila L. extracts had no human T-cell leukemia virus type 1-related symptoms, while those who were not administered Ficus pumila L. extracts had human T-cell leukemia virus type 1-related diseases and a significantly poorer prognosis. This suggests that the Ficus pumila L. extracts may show some utility against virus infection.</item>
        <item>article2</item>
        <item>article3</item>
        <item>article4</item>
        <item>article5</item>
        <item>article6</item>
        <item>article7</item>
        <item>article8</item>
        <item>article9</item>
        <item>article10</item>
        <item>article11</item>
        <item>article12</item>
        <item>article13</item>
        <item>article14</item>
        <item>article15</item>


    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
<<<<<<< HEAD
    <string name="password_hint">enter your password</string>
=======

>>>>>>> 3932bd286224c2e60bbc3d62ff328cb932c927fd
</resources>