<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Halisi Wellness</string>


    <string-array name="title_articles">

        <item>Ficus pumila L. improves the prognosis of patients infected with HTLV-1, an RNA virus</item>
        <item>Turmeric: Potential Health Benefits</item>
        <item>Genetically Modified Organisms</item>
        <item>Vanilla</item>
        <item>Pasta In Health Diet</item>
        <item>Choline</item>
        <item>Mycoprotein</item>
        <item>Cinnamon</item>
        <item>Fruits and Vegetables</item>



    </string-array>

    <string-array name="details_articles">

        <item>Human T-cell leukemia virus type 1 was isolated as the retrovirus to be identified in humans.
            Here, we focused on Ficus pumila L. as a factor that be effective against human T-cell leukemia virus type 1.
            The significant and novel findings is that symptoms of patients with drinking Ficus pumila L.
            extracts did not worsen despite a lack of aggressive pharmacotherapy against adult T-cell leukemia, a human T-cell leukemia virus type 1-associated myelopathy, or T-cell leukemia virus type 1 uveitis.
            Twenty-eight of the 194 inpatients who underwent showed high levels of human T-cell leukemia virus type 1.
            Among human T-cell leukemia virus type 1-infected patients, those who were administered Ficus pumila L. extracts had no human T-cell leukemia virus type 1-related symptoms, while those who were not administered Ficus pumila L.
            extracts had human T-cell leukemia virus type 1-related diseases and a significantly poorer prognosis. This suggests that the Ficus pumila L. extracts may show some utility against virus infection.</item>

        <item>Details of 21 clinical trials assessing the effectiveness of turmeric powder or curcuminoid-containing supplements on signs and symptoms of arthritis are included in Supplemental Digital Content 1, http://links.lww.com/NT/A27. A summary of these studies is presented in Table 1. Most of these trials evaluated patients with knee osteoarthritis, and the patients enrolled were predominantly females (75%). Patient populations were derived primarily from the Middle East and Asia. The trials measured both intensity of pain and improvements in physical functioning using several indices. The Western Ontario and McMaster Universities Osteoarthritis Index, the Lequesne Pain Functional Index, and the Japanese Knee Osteoarthritis Measure evaluate improvements in pain and functionality, whereas the visual analog scale measures severity of pain. The Disease Activity Score measures the number of swollen and tender joints; blood markers of inflammation, such as erythrocyte sedimentation rate and C-reactive protein (CRP); and the patient global assessment of health. The American College of Rheumatology survey measures similar criteria as the Disease Activity Score. The Clinician Global Impression of Change measures joint tenderness, crepitus, alignment, movement, and muscle wasting.</item>

        <item>Tools to improve organic crop operations and yields are needed.1 The economic, nutritional, and environmental benefits of genetically modified (GM) food may improve organic crop production. For that reason, we propose the removal of GM materials (ie, seeds and plantules [embryos beginning germination]) from the “excluded methods and procedures” for organic certification. In 1986, the US Executive Office of the President and the Office of Science and Technology Policy released the Coordinated Framework for Regulation of Biotechnology to regulate the use of GM, conventional, and organic materials in the United States. As defined in the Code of Federal Regulations (CFR), genetic modification is the “production of heritable improvements in plants or animals for specific uses, via either genetic engineering or other more traditional methods,” and a GM organism (GMO) is “an organism produced through these genetic modifications.” As opposed to conventional plant breeding practice, a gene from a different species is inserted into the plant cell. For example, Bt (Bacillus thuringiensis) corn contains genetic material from Bt, a bacterium that grows naturally in the soil. Bacillus thuringiensis produces crystal-like proteins during spore forming, which, when ingested by a susceptible insect, the crystals act like a poison. The benefit of these proteins is their specificity to some groups on insects, harming only crop pests and leaving beneficial insects alone. Moreover, they have no effects on mammals.2 Inserting genes from different species is one of the main issues of concern regarding the use of GMOs.</item>


        <item>The vanilla plant, Vanilla planifolia or Vanilla fragrans (family Orchidaceae), is native to Mexico and is cultivated in numerous sites worldwide, with Indonesia and Madagascar being major sources of production. Vanilla tahitensis and Vanilla pompona are other key species contributing to commercial vanilla production. The green vanilla beans harvested from the plants are essentially odorless and lacking flavor. It is during the curing process of ripening, drying, and conditioning that chemical and enzymatic reactions produce the distinctive flavor and aroma profiles of the different end products. These species provide vanilla products differing in quality and use. For example, V. pompona bean is of lesser quality and used more in the production of fragrances. On the other hand, V. planifolia and V. tahitensis exhibit stronger, more desirable aroma profiles. Vanilla extract is prepared by further macerating cured vanilla pods with a solution of ethanol and water to produce a finished flavoring product that must meet a specific Food and Drug Administration (FDA) standard of identity. Imitation or synthetic vanilla extract is a cheaper food flavoring synthesized from starting chemicals originating from less expensive entities, such as clove oil, spruce tree lignin, and a petrochemical-derived precursor. The price of natural vanilla extract can vary considerably. Practically speaking, retail real vanilla extract could cost several dollars per ounce depending on market forces, whereas imitation vanilla extract could cost several cents per ounce.</item>

        <item>Over the years, pasta has gained an unearned reputation as a contributor to health issues, such as weight gain, diabetes, and cardiovascular disease. The sustained popularity of low-carbohydrate diets has further propagated the belief that eating pasta is bad for health, but the evidence is insufficient to support these perceptions. Pasta has a long culinary history as one of the major components of the Mediterranean diet, which has been proven through years of research to be a healthy dietary pattern. Most dry pasta in the United States is enriched with iron, riboflavin, thiamine, and folic acid. A 2-oz serving of dry pasta (about 1 cup, cooked) supplies the equivalent of roughly 100 μg of folic acid, or 25% of the Daily Value, making it an excellent source of the B vitamin, and it is a good source of iron, providing about 10% of the Daily Value. Pasta’s unique profile as a low-cost, convenient, versatile, and nutritious food with a long shelf-life establishes an important role for pasta in meeting the nutrient needs of not only the United States, but globally as well.</item>

        <item>The name choline is derived from the Greek term for bile (ie, chole) because it was first isolated from ox bile in 1862. Its nutritional importance was not recognized until the 1930s, when deficiency was demonstrated to cause fatty liver disease in dogs and rats, which resolved when choline was reintroduced to the diet. Over the following decade, consensus emerged around the general essentiality of choline to prevent liver damage in several mammalian species, including the rat, dog, chicken, pig, rhesus monkey, and baboon.5 Recognition that choline is an essential nutrient for humans was further advanced in the 1980s by studies in men and women on parenteral nutrition who developed liver damage in its absence.5,6 A dietary requirement for choline was first demonstrated in healthy men participating in a depletion-repletion metabolic study.7 The Adequate Intake (AI) for choline was established by the Food and Nutrition Board of the National Academy of Medicine (NAM) (formerly the Institute of Medicine) in 1998, at a time when dietary intakes across the population were unknown for the nutrient. Traditionally, the AI reflects an observed or experimentally determined approximation or estimate of intake by a group (or groups) of healthy individuals.1,5 Adequate Intakes have been used when data to calculate an estimated average requirement (EAR) and recommended dietary allowance (RDA) are not available. Unlike this typical NAM approach, the development of the AI for choline was informed by the previously mentioned depletion-repletion study in adult men, in which deficiency resulted in liver damage.1,5 The AI for adults was calculated as 7 mg/kg times the reference weight of a man (76 kg) or woman (61 kg), with rounding based on prevention of liver damage. Upward adjustments during pregnancy and lactation were made based on the amount of choline accretion by the fetus and placenta and the amount secreted in human breast milk. For infants aged 0 to 6 months, the AI was set to reflect the observed mean intake of choline from consuming human breast milk (note: this value does not take into consideration the higher content of the colostrum) (Table 1).1 The dietary requirement for choline has not been revisited by NAM since 1998, despite a growing body of scientific literature. There is a need for dose-response studies across various populations to inform revision of the current Dietary Reference Intakes (DRIs) to include an EAR and RDA, so that accurate assessment of the amounts of individuals who are inadequate can be determined.</item>

        <item>In accordance with European Commission, nutrition claims that can be made for mycoprotein are as follows: (1) “high in protein,” that is, at least 20% of the energy value of the food is provided by protein; (2) “low in fat,” that is, contains no more than 3 g of fat per 100 g of solids; (3) “low in saturated fat,” that is, does not contain more than 1.5 g of saturated fatty acids per 100 g of solids; and (4) “high in fiber,” that is, contains at least 6 g of fiber per 100 g.16,17 It should, however, be noted that regulations vary among countries, and in US regulations, “high” means 20% of the Daily Value per reference amounts customarily consumed (RACC).18 Mycoprotein is an important provider of dietary fiber, containing around 5 g per RACC. Because the Daily Value for fiber in the United States is 25 g, mycoprotein would therefore meet the US standard for the claim of “high” in fiber.

As seen in Table 2, using US data for RACC19 and from the US Department of Agricutlure Food Composition Database,20 the nutritional profiles of plant- and animal-based food sources can be compared. Mycoprotein is lower in energy than some nonanimal protein sources. Protein levels in mycoprotein are similar to that of cooked chicken. With respect to protein, it should be noted that approximately 8% to 10% of the protein analyzed is nonprotein nitrogen. When looking at the RACC, mycoprotein has one of the lowest total fat and saturated fat profiles—providing less than 1 g of saturated fat per portion. It is also free from cholesterol and trans-fats.

As shown in Figure 3, mycoprotein is an important source of fiber. The dietary fiber present in mycoprotein is naturally occurring, and typically one-third of this is chitin (poly n-acetyl glucosamine) and two-thirds is β-glucan.21 Linear β-glucans (from cereals) and branched β-glucans (fungi; yeast) have been shown to have immunostimulating effects and participate in physiological processes related to the metabolism of fats in the human body.22,23 Using the RACC and US Department of Agricutlure Food Composition Database data, it seems that mycoprotein contains more fiber than almonds, black beans, chickpeas, and peanuts do. However, it should be considered that the fiber foods between these food substances vary, with nuts and legumes contributing important nondigestible carbohydrates and lignin that are intrinsic and intact in plants</item>

        <item>For centuries cinnamon has been a culinary spice and folk remedy for various maladies. In traditional medicines, its uses include for relief of gastrointestinal distress, arthritis, high blood pressure (BP), dermatitis, toothache, and colds; for improving menstrual irregularities; and for wound healing. Depending on the cultural culinary context, cinnamon is added to beverages, desserts, liqueurs, teas, chicken and lamb dishes, breads and pastries, and fruit preparations.1–3 Four species of the genus Cinnamomum are main contributors to its commercial applications. These are Cinnamomum verum (also known as Cinnamomum zeylanicum, Sri Lankan/Ceylon cinnamon), Cinnamomum cassia (also called Cinnamomum aromaticum, Chinese cinnamon), Cinnamomum burmannii (Indonesian/Java cinnamon), and Cinnamomum loureiroi (Saigon/Vietnamese cinnamon). The chemical profiles of the oils and other extracts derived from the dried inner bark of these different species exhibit varying levels of main constituents, which include cinnamaldehyde, cinnamic acid, coumarin, linalool, eugenol, caryophyllene, and polyphenol polymers.4–6 Recently, cinnamon supplements received increased attention for their use as adjuncts in treating high blood glucose and lipid levels and other symptoms of the metabolic syndrome.7–9 In the past decade, in particular, more clinical studies evaluated the efficacy of cinnamon toward these conditions, as well as toward polycystic ovary syndrome (PCOS) and inflammatory disorders. The current article provides a brief summary of these human trials, highlights recommendations based on current scientific evidence, and addresses issues for future research.</item>




    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>